Guide to the Jacques E. Levy Research Collection on Cesar Chavez
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
In addition to the transcripts, the files include copies of the notes Cesar Chavez used for his lecture series on the history of farm labor and the University of California Santa Barbara in 1992, correspondence between Levy and interviewees, as well as documentation relating to Levy's negotiations with the Chavez Foundation in sponsoring his work on the biography. There are eleven folders of Chavez's FBI files, which Levy requested through the Freedom of Information Act in 1993. Printed material relating to Chavez's death include clippings, and programs from the funeral.
Series VIII, Written Notes, 1968-1993 (boxes 41-42), is organized into six subseries: Negotiations, Jacques Levy Personal Papers, Jacques Levy Correspondence, Jacques Levy Research Notes, Book and Movie Outline, and Post 1975 Materials. Within each subseries, the subject files are arranged alphabetically. This series, which contains both original and photocopied material, includes unpublished notes on major negotiations with grape growers and others, correspondence with Cesar Chavez about writing the biography, discussing developments in the union, as well as personal matters. Other correspondents include Jim Drake, Senator George Murphy, editors, literary agents, and librarians at Wayne State University. Levy discusses his work on the book with these people and gathers information in these letters. Personal papers of Levy's include copies of speeches made about Chavez and the farm labor movement, a book proposal, and proposals for a movie based on Cesar's life.
Series IX, Levy Inventory, 1998 (box 43), is the original inventory created by Levy that accompanied the collection when it was acquired by the Beinecke Library. Levy's inventory lists each item in each folder, provides lengthy descriptions of the content of the audiotapes and notebooks, and lists clippings individually by title, date, and newspaper. The inventory does not provide current box and folder information needed to locate individual items or groups of material: for that, consult the box and folder listings laid out in Series I-VIII and X. Other differences of detail between the finding aid and inventory: Levy's description of each file makes no distinction between copies and originals in terms of assigning dates; the Beinecke finding aid lists copies of original material as undated. The Levy inventory also indicates whether an audiotape has been partially transcribed, partially paraphrased, or not transcribed at all.
Series X, Assassination Plot, 1971-1974 (boxes 44-49), is currently restricted. For further information, please contact the curator. The series is organized into seven subseries: Audiotapes, Book Material, Plot Files, Plot Material, Shears Tapes, "The Snitch", and Transcripts. This series contains both original and photocopied material relating to Levy's investigation of a growers' plot to kill Chavez, as revealed by informant Larry Shears, and Levy's suspicion of a subsequent cover-up by government and law enforcement officials on behalf of prominent growers. Most of this material was never published. There are 39 audiotapes; 20 of them (and 6 duplicates) are surreptitiously taped phone conversations made by Larry Shears, a police informant, to document a plot to kill Chavez in 1971. Each side of these audiotapes was numbered individually. The other audiotapes in the collection are tapes of Levy's interview of Larry Shears, tapes of Larry Shears' polygraph test, and interviews by others of Larry Shears. The audiotapes made by Shears were turned over to the police and FBI, and transcripts were made as well. There are transcripts for almost all of the audiotapes in this series, and there are also transcripts present for which there are no corresponding audiotapes. After reformatting, some audiotapes were discovered to be duplicates, necessitating a rearrangement of the audiotapes and a gap in the folder numbering.
The subject files in the Book Material, Plot Files, Plot Material, and Transcripts subseries are arranged alphabetically, and include transcripts, copies of court transcripts, Levy's notes of his meetings with authorities and Larry Shears, correspondence relating to the plot, a polygraph report on Larry Shears, a typescript by Levy detailing the plot, and a screenplay by Maurice Hatton based on events as researched by Levy, entitled "The Snitch." The Plot Files were apparently files created by Levy during his research on the plot, and Plot Material is apparently files of others obtained by Levy. The assassination plot is also chronicled in Series III, Jacques E. Levy's Notebook Collection, notebooks 32-41, 43, 45, 53-56, 60-61, 64, 70, and 89.
Oversize, boxes 50-52, contains material from Series V, VI, and VII, and is organized in box order.
Restricted Fragile in boxes 53-76 and broadside folder 1043 may only be consulted with permission of the appropriate curator. Preservation photocopies or photographic prints for reference use have been substituted in the main files. The original audiotapes are restricted. Reference copies on CD-ROM have been made.
Restricted Material in box 77 may only be consulted with the permission of the appropriate curator.
CD-ROM Reference Copies of Audio Tapes contains the box listing for reference copies from Series I, II, VI, VII and X, and is in folder order.
Appendix A: Discrepancies Between Levy Inventory and Beinecke Finding Aid
Series I, file 14: William "Bill" Kircher. File found empty.
Series I, tape 111, Cesar Chavez Bonn, West Germany talk continued, Copenhagen press conference, Brussell press conference: Brussells press conference is described as being present on side B of audiotape, which is mostly blank.
Series II, Tape 57: JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez was found to be blank.
Series IV, file 6: Missing AWOC/labor contractors agreement used between 1963 and 1965 (8p.).
Series VI, file 60: Missing clipping number 2: Time cover story, "Campaign '74" 10/21/74.
Series VIII, folder 781: Missing audiotape GH Tape 2 (George Higgins).
Series X, Cassette 21-22: During reformatting, cassette side 22 was found to be recorded pop music of the period.
Series X, Cassettes 29-40: There are duplicates of each of these audiotapes, not mentioned in Levy inventory.
Series X: There is a "Cassette 7-8 Barger case" not mentioned in Levy inventory.
Series X, Plot Tape 5: Described on Levy inventory as "Shears test" is actually an interview with Levy, and Levy's indexing of his tapes. A transcript is also available for side A.
Series X, Plot Tape 8: There are two more tapes which together duplicate the information on this audiocassette, not mentioned in the Levy inventory.
Series X: There are cassettes marked "Cassette 3" and "Cassette 6" not mentioned in the Levy inventory.
Appendix B: Notes Regarding Reformatting Audiotapes to CD-ROM
The audiotapes were reformatted to CD-ROM in 2001. Levy used audiotapes of varying lengths. 40 and 60 minute audiotapes were reformatted onto one CD. 90, 100, and 120 minute audiotapes were reformatted onto two CDs, one CD per side. These CDs share a folder number and are identified as "1 of 2" and "2 of 2." No filtering or equalization was used during the reformatting, in order that the audiotapes replicate the tapes as closely as possible. Each CD carries two tracks: the recorded leader with copyright information, and the contents of the audiotape. The following notes reflect action taken by the reformatter during this work.
Folder 54, 2 of 2, Tape 54, Cesar Chavez, Night union meeting, Manuel Chavez: The CD has three tracks, rather than the usual two, due to a 9 minute gap after the first 1:15.
Folder 55, 1 of 2, Tape 55, Cesar Chavez, JEL notes: The CD has three tracks due to an inadvertent push of the button during reformatting. Track 3 is just a continuation of track 2.
Folder 57, 2 of 2, Tape 57, Cesar Chavez, JEL notes, Cesar Chavez and others: The first 3:53 of the tape are blank. The CD starts with the first sound on the tape.
Folder 64, Tape 62 (#2), Dr. Jerome Lackner: This audiotape was not reformatted to a CD. Dr. Lackner's comments on Cesar Chavez's health after a 4 day fast runs for 2:40 minutes.
Folder 83, Tape 79 (#g2), Cesar Chavez: The first 9:53 of the tape are blank. The CD starts with the first sound on the tape.
Folder 109, Tape 105. Helen Chavez continued, Richard Chavez: The audiotape is identified as this, but the actual recording is of Jacques Levy on modern French tapestry maker Jean Lurçat.
Folder 115, Tape 111, Cesar Chavez Bonn, West Germany talk continued, Copenhagen press conference, [Brussell press conference?]: Brussells press conference described as being present on audiotape is not there.
Folder 121, Tape 117, JEL notes: The first 1:09 of the tape are blank. The CD starts with the first sound on the tape.
Folder 125, 2 of 2, Tape 121, JEL notes: The CD has three tracks because the audiotape folded onto itself. The reformatter stopped the CD for the two minutes of bad backward tape.
Folder 126, 1 of 2, Tape 122, Senator Kennedy speech, JEL notes, memorial mass with Joan Baez: The CD has three tracks, due to a three minute gap after the first 13 minutes (after the Kennedy speech and before the question and answer with Kennedy).
Folder 213, Tape 6, Anti UFW rally, Salinas Valley: The CD has seven tracks, due to the poor condition of the audiotape. The reformatter stopped and started the CD while rerunning the audiotape six times before being forced to stop the transfer completely.
Folder 236, Tape 29, JEL interviewed on KTRB: The audiotape side B was marked "con't." but the side was blank.
Folder 255j, Tape 57, JEL reading book manuscript to Cesar Chavez: The audiotape is blank on both sides.
Folder 518, 1 of 2, CALRA Tape 2, Jerry Cohen and UFW attorneys Sandy Nathan and Tony Gaenslen: The first 6:42 minutes of the tape are blank. The CD starts with the first sound on the tape.
Folder 636, PMR MG Tape 6, Marshall Ganz: The audiotape side B has a set up but the rest of the tape is blank.
Folder 650, PMR CH Tape 5, Chris Hartmire: The audiotape side B was marked as a continuation of side A, but was blank.
Folder 835, cassette 17-18: Side 17 is just a test side; there is no information after 1:28 minutes.
Folder 841a, Cassette 29-30 John Tudor: Track 2, labeled Cass 29 is actually cassette side 30 and track 3, labeled Cass 30 is actually cassette side 29.
Agricultural industries -- California; Labor leaders -- United States; Labor unions -- Migrant agricultural laborers -- United States; Mexican American labor union members; Mexican American migrant agricultural laborers; Audiovisual materials; Audiotapes; Oral histories (document genres); Labor leaders -- United States; Chavez, Cesar, 1927-1993; Levy, Jacques E.; Chavez family; California ( Alatorre-Zenovich-Dunlap-Berman Agricultural Labor Relations Act of 1975); United Farm Workers
- Principal Cesar Chavez Tape Collection, 1969-1976; Series I; 3.99; (14 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I, Principal Cesar Chavez Tape Collection, is organized into two subseries: Audiotapes and Transcripts, and contains original audiotapes and partial transcripts made and organized by Levy. The audiotapes are restricted; reference copies on CD-ROM have been made. Jacques Levy's initials are used instead of his full name.
  - AUDIOTAPES
    - Principal Audiotapes
      Conditions Governing Access
      Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies can be found in boxes 78-84. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Tape 1. Cesar Chavez first interview, 1969 Feb 4; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365752)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 1-49, stored in: box 1, folder 132
      - Tape 2. History teacher Jim Bush and students interview Chavez and others, Delano-Sacramento march, undated; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365760)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1182-1202 and File 27, stored in: box 3, folder 157 and box 6, folder 200
      - Tape 3. Larry Itliong, his early youth, 1969 Apr 4; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365778)
        Transcript: File 12 LI: 1-9, stored in: box 5, folder 185
      - Tape 4. Larry Itliong continued / Dolores Huerta, Fred Ross interviews, 1969 Apr 4; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365786)
        Transcript: File 12 LI: 9-14, File 11 DH: 1, File 24 FR 1-19, stored in: box 5, folders 183-185, and box 6, folder 196
      - Tape 5. Larry Itliong interview, Delano and Dolores Huerta in car to Coachella, 1969 April 6; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365794)
        Transcript: File 12 LI: 14-39, File 11 DH: 1-12, stored in: box 5, folders 183-185
      - Tape 6. Dolores Huerta continued / Gilbert Padilla, Homer Bigart interviewing Jim Drake, 1969 April 6-7; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365802)
        Transcript: File 11 DH: 12-24, File 19 GP: 1-35, File 7 JD: 1-3, stored in: box 5, folders 177, 183-184, and 189
      - Tape 7. Homer Bigart interview concluded, Paul Espinosa interview / Dolores Huerta and Doug Adair, 1969 April 6-7; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365810)
        Transcript: File 7 JD: 3, File 9 PE: 1-9, File 11 DH: 24-66, stored in: box 5, folders 177, 179, and 183-184
      - Tape 8. Dolores Huerta continued / Dolores Huerta and Fred Ross outside office, 1969 April 7; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365828)
        Transcript: File 11 DH: 66-97, stored in: box 5, folders 183-184
      - Tape 9. Cesar Chavez guard training class, Cesar Chavez and Bob McMillan, Philippine Labor Attaché at Indio union rally, speeches by Itliong, Bill Kircher and Cesar Chavez, 1969 April 7-13; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365836)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1147-1158, Volume 2 CC: 518-528, Volume 3 CC: 1159-1181, File 20, stored in: box 3, folder 156, box 2, folder 141, and 5, folder 192
      - Tape 10. Cesar Chavez speech continued at Coachella rally, union meeting in Indio / Dolores Huerta trip to Stockton, 1969 April 13; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365844)
        Transcript: File 11 DH: 97-143, stored in: box 5, folders 183-184
      - Tape 11. Dolores Huerta trip to Stockton continued, 1969 April 13; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365851)
        Transcript: File 11 DH: 143-153, stored in: box 5, folders 183-184
      - Tape 12. Michael L. Klein of UAW / Hijnio Rangel in Detroit, 1969 April 29; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365869)
        Transcript: File 13 MK: 1-38, File 23 HR: 1-12, stored in: box 5, folder 186 and box 6, folder 195
      - Tape 13. Dr. Philip Mason, 1969 April 29; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365877)
        Transcript: File 16 PM: 1-10, stored in: box 6, folder 188
      - Tape 14. Cesar Chavez early life, 1969 May 6; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365885)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 50-66, stored in: box 1, folder 132
      - Tape 15. Richard Chavez I, 1969 May 7; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365893)
        Transcript: File 6 RC: 1-28, stored in: box 5, folder 176
      - Tape 16. Richard Chavez I continued, 1969 May 7; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365901)
      - Tape 17. Cesar Chavez, union meeting, 1969 May 9; 1 (Box 53, Item barcode 39002099365919)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC 67-75, Volume 1 CC: 85-93, stored in: box 1, folders 133
      - Tape 18. Cesar Chavez, 1969 May 10-14; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366255)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 75-85, Volume 1 CC: 93-104, stored in: box 1, folders 132-133
      - Tape 19. Cesar Chavez, Calexico rally with Senator Yarborough, Bill Kircher, Senator Mondale, Senator Ted Kennedy, the Reverend Ralph Abernathy, and Cesar Chavez, 1969 May 15-18; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366263)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC 105-115, Volume 3 CC: 1114-1122, stored in: box 1, folder 133 and box 3, folder 155
      - Tape 20. Senator Ted Kennedy in Calexico, JEL (Jacques E. Levy) notes, Rita Medina, 1969 May 18-22; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366271)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1122-1134, File 18 RM: 1-11, stored in: box 3, folders 155-156, box 5, folder 190
      - Tape 21. Rita Medina (Cesar's older sister) continued, 1969 May 22; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366289)
        Transcript: File 18 RM: 11-32, stored in: box 5, folder 190
      - Tape 22. Fred Ross in [San Francisco], 1969 May 28; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366297)
        Transcript: File 24 FR: 33-52, stored in: box 6, folder 196
      - Tape 23. Larry Itliong, Coachella Strike interviews and JEL notes, 1969 June 18-20; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366305)
        No transcript
      - Tape 24. JEL notes, Jim Drake, Cesar Chavez to Coachella strikers, Cesar Chavez in Delano, 1969 June 21-23; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366313)
        Transcript: Volume 3 CC: 1135-1145, Volume 1 CC: 115-120, stored in: box 3, folder 156 and box 1, folder 133
      - Tape 25. Cesar Chavez continued, 1969 June 23; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366321)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 120-126, stored in: box 1, folder 133
      - Tape 26. Cesar Chavez, 1969 June 25; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366339)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 126-156, stored in: box 1, folder 133
      - Tape 27. Cesar Chavez continued, U.S. California Senator Murphy, 1969 June 25-July 1; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366347)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 156-163, Volume 1 CC: 212-229, stored in: box 1, folders 133-136
      - Tape 28. Cesar Chavez continued, 1969 June 27-28; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366354)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 164-190, stored in: box 1, folder 134
      - Tape 29. Cesar Chavez continued, "Maria," Richard Chavez and Cesar Chavez, 1969 June 28-29; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366362)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 190-212, stored in: box 1, folder 134
      - Tape 30. Cesar Chavez continued, Cesar Chavez and Helen Chavez, 1969 July 1-3; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366370)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 229-259, stored in: box 1, folder 135
      - Tape 31. Cesar Chavez continued, 1969 July 3-9; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366388)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 259-311, stored in: box 1, folders 135-136
      - Tape 32. Cesar Chavez continued, Cesar Chavez new interview, 1969 July 9-12; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366396)
      - Tape 33. Cesar Chavez concluded, 1969 July 12; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366404)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 311-319, stored in: box 1, folder 136
      - Tape 34. Cesar Chavez, his two brothers, two sisters, and both parents, 1969 July 26; 1 (Box 54, Item barcode 39002099366412)
        Transcript: File 10 Family Gathering FG: 1-106, stored in: box 5, folders 180-182
      - Tape 35. Cesar Chavez, his two brothers, two sisters, and both parents, 1969 July 26; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366420)
      - Tape 36. Cesar Chavez, his two brothers, two sisters, and both parents, 1969 July 26; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366438)
      - Tape 37. Cesar Chavez, his two brothers, two sisters, and both parents, 1969 July 26; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366446)
      - Tape 38. Cesar Chavez for Playboy article, 1969 September 16; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366453)
        Transcript: File 21 Playboy 1-18, stored in: box 5, folder 193
      - Tape 39. Cesar Chavez to and from North Hollywood, 1969 September 20; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366461)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 319-344, stored in: box 1, folder 136
      - Tape 40. Cesar Chavez concluded, 1969 September 20; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366479)
      - Tape 41. Cesar Chavez, 1969 December 8; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366487)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 433-472, stored in: box 1, folders 138-139
      - Tape 42. Elaine Elinson, JEL notes, 1969 August 25; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366495)
        Transcript: File 8 EE: 1-24, stored in: box 5, folder 178
      - Tape 43. Cesar Chavez and Bill Kircher, 1970 February 12; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366503)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 344-380, stored in: box 1, folders 136-137
      - Tape 44. Cesar Chavez and Bill Kircher continued, Cesar Chavez, Santa Barbara, 1970 February 12-13; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366511)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 381-420, File 28, stored in: box 1, folders 137-138, box 6, folder 201
      - Tape 45. Cesar Chavez continued, JEL notes, Bill Kircher, Santa Barbara, 1970 February 13-March 22; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366529)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 421-433, File 14 WK: 1-9, File 29, stored in: box 1, folder 138, box 6, folder 202
      - Tape 46. Cesar Chavez after signing Gallo contract, 1970 April 18; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366537)
        Transcript: Volume 1 CC: 473-491, stored in: box 1, folders 139-140
      - Tape 47. JEL with John Lewis, Martha Schaffer, Sam Kushner, undated; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366545)
        Transcript: File 15 Lewis: 1-47, stored in: box 5, folder 187
      - Tape 48. Cesar Chavez, 1970 May 23; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366552)
        Transcript: Volume 1 & 2 CC: 492-517, stored in: box 1, folder 140 and box 2, folder 141
      - Tape 49. Mack Lyons, 1970 June 3; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366560)
      - Tape 50. Mack Lyons continued, questions for family session, 1970 June 3; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366578)
      - Tape 51. Cesar Chavez, JEL Notes, 1970 June 18-19; 1 (Box 55, Item barcode 39002099366586)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 584-628, stored in: box 2, folders 142-143
      - Tape 52. Cesar Chavez concluded, JEL Notes, Cesar at Stardust Union meeting, Cesar back from La Paz, Jerry Cohen, 1970 June 19-24; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366594)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 632-671, stored in: box 2, folders 143-144
      - Tape 53. Cesar Chavez concluded, Cesar Chavez to Fresno and Bill Kircher, 1970 June 24-25; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366602)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 671-698, stored in: box 2, folder 144
      - Tape 54. Cesar Chavez, night union meeting, Manuel Chavez, 1970 July 1-4; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366610)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 699-733, stored in: box 2, folder 145
      - Tape 55. Cesar Chavez at Stardust, JEL notes, 1970 July 8-11; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366628)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 734-762, box 2, folders 145-146
      - Tape 56. Cesar Chavez continued, Cesar Chavez speech at Telacu, JEL notes, Union work meeting, 1970 July 11-13; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366636)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 762-779, stored in: box 2, folder 146
      - Tape 57. Cesar Chavez Stardust, JEL notes, mass and announcement on growers' negotiation, 1970 July 13-16; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366644)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 780-805, stored in: box 2, folders 146-147
      - Tape 57 (C-D). Phone calls to boycotters, 1970 July 16; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366651)
      - Tape 58. Philip Feick, Jr., JEL notes, Cesar Chavez, Cesar Chavez and Bill Kircher, 1970 July 10-17; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366669)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 805-836, stored in: box 2, folders 147-148
      - Tape 59. JEL's son Brian; William Kircher; Fred Ross; Cesar Chavez to Santa Paula; Cesar Chavez, Tony Newhall, and Fred Ross; Cesar Chavez speech; JEL notes; Dolores Huerta and Marshall Ganz, 1970 July 20-27; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366677)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 836-858, File 24 FR: 53-61, File 11 DH: 152-159, stored in: box 2, folder 148, box 6, folder 196, and box 5, folders 183-184
      - Tape 60. Salinas Press conference, JEL notes, signing ceremony at end of strike in Delano, transcript of press conference, Cesar Chavez on phone, 1970 July 29; 1 (Box 56, Item barcode 39002099366685)
        Transcript: Volume 2 CC: 859-886, stored in: box 2, folders 148-149